and let's move on to another topic let's move on to another topic
y vamos a otro tema vamos a otro tema
that is also quite hot and that is
que está también bastante candente y es
the topic of them denouncing wbc.
el tema de que están funando a wbc
Uh well let's see I
Eh bueno a ver yo
personally have to tell you something and let's
personalmente tengo que deciros algo y a
see if you agree with
ver si estáis de acuerdo ustedes conmigo
me, wcol seems like a
a mí wcol me parece un
guy who is not a bad person I do
tío no mala persona
n't think he is, let's see [ __ ] it's that of course
no creo que sea a ver [__] es que claro
now you'll tell me he's not a bad person but let's
ahora me diréis no es mala persona pero
see westcol
a ver westcol
salsería of course he does
salsería claro es que
let's see how I explain this to you look I
hace a ver cómo os explico esto mira yo
have a video talking about wbc okay it's
tengo un vídeo hablando de wbc vale es
a video that's almost 50 minutes long compiling
un vídeo de casi 50 minutos recopilando
a lot of homophobia machismo
un montón de homofobia de machismo
insults or rather it crosses any line
insulto o sea traspasa cualquier línea
no So you say a bad person
no Entonces tú dices una mala persona
Notice that in the
Fíjate que en el tema
westcol issue okay I think what he lacks
westcol vale Yo creo que lo que le falta
is culture education eh And he is With all due
es cultura educación eh Y está Con todo
respect eh or rather With all due respect
el respeto eh o sea Con todo el respeto
in the world to wherever he was raised
del mundo a a donde se haya criado al
wherever or rather but I think they have
lugar donde o sea pero creo que tienen
normalized things that are not
cosas normalizadas que no son las
correct okay that of of of telling it
correctas vale eso de de de de contarlo
as if it were a joke to him eh Well yes
como si fuera una gracia a él eh Pues si
my Well now let's see some clicks
mi Bueno ahora vamos a ver algunos clics
okay but  look, he doesn't have an act,
vale pero fíjate que no tiene un acto
which maybe he has and it hasn't come out
que a lo mejor lo tiene y no ha salido
all of a sudden if he has an act, well it would
cl de repente si tiene un acto Pues
n't surprise me either cku like
tampoco me sorprendería cku como lo de
coku no, he doesn't have an act like coku
coku no no tiene un acto como el de coku
coku has an act which is the photo
coku tiene un acto que es lo de la foto
no and all that stuff about that live
no y todo el rollo ese del directo aquel
and and so on
y y demás
Okay,
Vale
but I don't know if he's bad, I don't know if he has a
pero no sé si es malo no sé si tiene un
bad core if he has an evil of doing
mal fondo si tiene una maldad de hacer
harm due to a lack of culture, evolution and
daño a falta de cultura evolución y y
things like that, you know, I mean, for example
cosas así me entiendes o sea por ejemplo
in the case of czu eh I think that I think I do
en el caso de czu eh yo creo que yo creo
n't know him maybe it's not that he's
no lo conozco a lo mejor no es que sea
a bad person he gets along with a lot of
una mala persona se lleva bien con mucha
people and all that stuff, I don't know
gente y todo el rollo ese no lo sé vale
okay maybe it's also an issue of
a lo mejor también es un tema de las
things that they have normalized but I don't
cosas que tien normalizada pero no lo
see it worse than, I mean, when it comes to complaining, I don't
veo peor que o sea puestos a funar no lo
see it worse than what happened with westcol, what happened with
veo peor que lo de westcol que lo de
cocu, okay, I mean, to me, suddenly they
cocu vale o sea a mí que de repente
come in and boo him Like that when Well, kcu was
entren y lo abuen Así cuando Bueno a kcu
booed too, no, but of course
si lo abuchearon también no pero claro a
ccu was not at the presentation where they
ccu en la presentación no fue donde lo
booed him, they booed him when when
abuchearon lo abuchearon ya cuando
the  funa got intense Because
cuando la funa se puso intensa Porque
a lot of people didn't know about wcol
mucha gente no lo sabía de wcol todo el
everyone knows what it's like they
mundo sabe cómo
would have brought chupetin Trujillo into
es hubieran metido a chupetin Trujillo a
the evening angry face no idea sidereal
la velada cara enfadada ni idea sideral
no idea what that is
ni idea qué es eso
even Abi blanque to czu Abi blanque To
incluso Abi blanque a czu Abi blanque A
czu what did Abi say about ccu I didn't remember I
czu qué dijo Abi de ccu no recordaba o
mean I know it was Abi that she messed
sea sé que Abi fue lo de que se metió
with Auro And that Draco Thank you so much
con Auro Y eso Draco Muchísimas gracias
for that member a kiss
por ese miembro un beso
friend How bad no
amigo Qué mal no
[Music]
[Música]
good night How
buenas noches Cómo
are you Well Welcome to the two
estás Bueno Bienvenidos a los dos
westcol you've already given the finger to
westcol ya le has metido una peineta a
the people no they
la gente no ellos
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
started how bad no how bad you've already
empezaron qué mal no qué mal
given it a greeting to the people
le has metido ya un saludo a la gente
direct no yes no
directo no sí no
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
yes How bad How bad he's a legend here if you
si Qué mal Qué mal es una leyenda aquí
understand me I'm not fighting with
si me entienden no estoy peleando con
any
cualquier
[ __ ] obviously I don't play at
huevón evidentemente no juego de
home very well very well I don't
local muy bien muy bien No
understand
entiendo
[ __ ] to see you out of [ __ ] No that's what he
[__] a ver salido de [__] No eso lo
said clearly it's that we are we're
ha dicho claro es que estamos estamos
bringing a person to the Main who of course
trayendo a una persona al Main que claro
in his live shows normalizes well well
que en sus directos normaliza pues pues
all these things of
pues todas estas cosas
course  even drugs no I mean wcol with his
claro incluso drogas no O sea wcol con
girlfriend he didn't get high on drugs
la novia no se puso como a drogarse en
live we saw that
un directo eso lo vimos
no of
no
course of course it's just that there's a lot of
Claro claro sea es que es mucha
fabric a lot of
tela mucha
fabric what this audience is crazy eh
tela lo de lo de este público es loco eh
gref Welcome to the evening of the year
gref Bienvenido a la velada del año
Thank you evening of the year let's see if it were a
Gracias velada del año a ver si fuera un
fight look at you no eh in one thing it does
combate fíjate tú no eh en una cosa sí
look bad but however if it
se ve mal pero sin embargo si
were a fight like or I mean a tournament
fuera un combate como o sea un torneo
like El Jordy wl there on the contrary
como el de El jordy wl ahí al contrario
no there it's a pulse to see who has the most
no ahí es un pulso a ver quién tiene más
criminal record And who has killed
antecedentes penales Y a quién ha matado
more people but of course this is supposed to be
a más gente pero claro esto se supone
from a streamer who is whiter
que es de streamer que es más blanquito
and such and suddenly p puts you in ccu now
y tal y de repente p te mete a ccu ahora
p puts you in West
p te mete a West
call of
call
course surely Colombia will be the
claro seguramente Colombia sea el
next country I visit the truth there
siguiente país que visite la verdad allá
in Colombia yes we receive it well like
en Colombia sí lo recibimos bieno como
this
esta
[ __ ] the
[__] la
reality there are values ​​there are values ​​Yes you
realidad hay valores hay valores Sí me
understand me there are values ​​daddy there in
entiendes hay valores papi allá en
Colombia go for us to show them
Colombia valla para nosotros mostrarles
How do I know even if we are rivals hesc
Cómo se aunque seamos rivales hesc
I hope we can share there also
Espero que podamos compartir allí tampo
too much public the Colombian public
demasiado público el público colombiano
seems Better than the Spanish 100% to
te parece Mejor que el español 100% al
already fought in my
ya pele en mi
event alana fought my event alana fought
evento alana pele mi evento alana peleó
Here I also fought event yana alana
Aquí también pele evento yana alana todo
everyone received her you can ask
el mundo la recibió le puede preguntar a
her here those who fight play as
ella aquí los que pelean juegan de
visitors because here there is a lot of home court you
visitante porque aquí hay mucha localía
understand do you think there is more home court
me entiende crees que hay más localía
than in other countries for example well for
que en otros países por ejemplo pues por
example when someone comes and
ejemplo nosotros cuando va alguien y nos
visits us we receive them as they should
visita lo recibimos como se debe
We are kind people if you
Nosotros somos personas amables si me
understand me then here obviously they do not
entiende entonces acá obviamente no
receive them the same way it is not an
reciben de la misma manera no es una
excuse because there is no problem I can
excusa porque no hay problema Yo puedo
have a lot of people here yelling at me talking
tener mucha gente acá gritándome
[ __ ] to me I do not give a
hablándome [__] no me importa un
[ __ ] if you understand me it is the reality I
[__] si me entiende es la realidad yo
am telling grefi I am
le estoy diciendo a grefi le estoy
talking to you go to my country so you can see how they
hablando vaya a mi país para que veas có
receive it But wescol do you think that if
lo reciben Pero wescol tú crees que si
evening 5 had been presented in
la velada 5 se hubiera presentado en
Colombia and our fight had been presented
Colombia y se presenta nuestro combate
the Colombian public would have snorted at me
el público colombiano a mí me hubiera
or applauded me he does not have
buche o me hubiera aplaudido no tiene No
Gref does not have the history that wc has well
tiene gref el historial que tiene wc
brother look I repeat I have had I have
pues brother vea le vuelvo a repetir yo
my own event and
he tenido Yo tengo mi propio evento y lo
we have done it in Colombia and in the event
hemos hecho en Colombia y en el evento
people from abroad have fought he has
ha peleado personas del extranjero tiene
veneers he has veneer the wcol does not  in the
carillas tiene carilla el wcol no en los
teeth he did not fight against a very
dientes no peleó contra una persona muy
famous person like you here there in
famosa así como usted aquí allá en
Colombia and the two of you had the same
Colombia y los dos tuvieron el mismo
support Because obviously When someone
apoyo Porque obviamente Cuando alguien
comes one has to travel one has to
viene uno tiene que viajar uno tiene que
take the time one has to get
tomarse el tiempo uno tiene que llegar
here if you know what I mean We are all here
aquí si me entiende Todos aquí estamos
putting in our time
poniendo de nuestro de nuestro tiempo
to make this show possible
para para para hacer este show posible
if you know what I mean There we know that here they don't
si me entiende Allá sabemos eso aquí no
know that's what I'm saying it
lo saben es lo que yo estoy diciendo
's very clear but it's not because
está bien claro pero es que no es porque
you travel or because you come from another place
tu viajes o porque vengas de otro sitio
or something like that of course it's because it's
o algo por el estilo claro es porque
you it's because it's you because you have
eres tú es porque eres tú porque tienes
the history that you have attitude that yesterday
el historial que tienes actitud que ayer
had this mini deal that calqui IB with with with with
tuvo el mini trati este que calqui IB
wescol and with some
con con con con wescol y con algunas
people seems like [ __ ] to me it doesn't
personas me parece una [__] no me
identify me at all it disgusts me and
identifica para nada me da asco y
any person who criticizes that type
cualquier persona que critique ese tipo
of attitude should know that I am on their
de actitudes que sepa que yo estoy en su
team and I don't care that that
equipo y a mí me da igual que eso haya
was in Spain because it made me even more ashamed
sido en España porque a mí más vergüenza
even more ashamed
aún me dio más vergüenza aún me dio
Because everything wesc said there was
Porque todo lo que dijo wesc ahí fue
real and whoever is hurt by the attitude
real y a quien le duela qu le actitud
that he had yesterday I mean support Agustín
que ayer tuvo el o sea apoya Agustín
support wescor support wescor but let's see
apoya wescor apoya wescor pero a ver
mm how  you see it, I mean because
mm cómo lo veis ustedes o sea porque
to a certain extent the public knows. Look, I
hasta cierto punto que el público
understand that it's uncomfortable, no,
abee A ver entiendo que es incómodo no
but in the end, how do you control that? That
pero al final tú cómo controlas eso eso
's not ibai's fault, it's the public,
no es culpa de ibai sea es el público
no, you're in a play and the
no tú estás en una obra de teatro y el
public boos, applauds, and ole. I don't know
público abuchea aplaude e ole No sé lo
what, what you feel like,
que lo que les apetece
not a situation that you remember, very
no una situación que recuerdes muy
uncomfortable,
incómoda
buah, baba, one of the current ones, baba. Yesterday, yesterday,
buah baba una de actual baba ayer ayer
I got a little uncomfortable with the evening, it
yo me incomod un poco con la velada por
was quite uncomfortable, in the
pas fue bastante incómodo es en el
last fight, there was a guy who wouldn't
último combate había un chico que no
stop arguing with wescol, seriously,
paraba de discutir con wescol en serio
but the public, I
pero que en el público o
mean, the public suddenly yelled at him 14 times and
sea públ de repente le gritó 14 veces y
each time he yelled it was more uncomfortable
cada vez que gritaba eraa más incómoda
than the previous one and apart from that, everyone kept
que la anterior y aparte todo el mundo
quiet when he yelled, it was like,
se callaba cuando gritaba era como por
we're letting him speak clearly because, I
le estamos dejando hablar claro porque o
mean, that's already making a note, one thing is
sea ya eso S es da la nota una cosa es
a boo, but now this guy is yelling
un abucheo pero ya el tío este gritando
every moment, one thing, let him yell
a cada momento una cosa que grite una
once, but now it's making a note, then
vez pero ya si está dando la nota ya ahí
security or whatever should have cut it off, but so what, and they didn't
seguridad o lo que fuera pero y qu y no
kick this guy out  Uncle I think not
lo echaron a este tío Yo creo que no
until the last moment I heard it is that
hasta el último momento yo lo escuché es
besides how it was like the end I
que aparte como era como el final yo
think that people thought they were going to
creo que la gente pensaba ya van a
fire him and they didn't throw him out anymore You know No but he
despedir y ya no lo echan sabes No pero
spent the time arguing and also the other one
se la pasó discutiendo y también el otro
gave him feedback so there was then it was
le le daba feedback entonces
part of the show I was
había entonces formaba parte del show I
biting it is that a moment happened that the
picando es que pasó un momento que el
kid said to fight with Manolo and
chico dijo que se pelee con Manolo y
everyone Ah but Manolo was the
todo el mundo Ah pero Manolo era el
kid that nobody knew who Manolo was
chaval que nadie sabía quién era Manolo
and suddenly wescol said He is a dwarf a
y de repente wescol dijo Es un enano una
situation Total that they are releasing a clip
situación Total que están sacando clip
of wescol like
de wescol como
this you know what bro I have to
este sabes qué bro yo tengo que
get myself a girlfriend that works in
conseguirme es una novia que trabaje en
a call center something like that that works in a
un call center una cosa así que trabaje
call center of course or a girlfriend that
call center en claro o una novia que
works at H Center or that works at the
trabaje en H Center o que trabaje en el
success as a cashier a girlfriend that works at
éxito de cajera una novia que trabaja en
the success as a cashier I can humiliate her and I
el éxito de cajera la puedo humillar y
can treat her badly and she will never
la puedo tratar mal y nunca me va a
leave me you are not totally wrong
dejar no estás totalmente equivocado
because I am going to support her mother
porque yo le voy a mantener la mamá
So you know that if I leave her her mother will be
Entonces ya sabe que si le dejo la mamá
poor no no no no the
queda pobre no no no no empieza la
strategy begins you take the block I
estrategia usted coge se la cuadra le
told him he says let's get your mother out of the
dije a le dice saquemos a su mamá del
neighborhood take her out of the neighborhood  makes you
barrio la saca del barrio la pone a
live
vivir
well is that we hadn't seen it eh we had
bien es que no lo habíamos visto eh ese
n't seen that one It's that it's that it's that this is the
no lo habí Es que es que es que es la
normality of Wescol it's that this is
normalidad de wescol
the normality of Wescol And this
es que es la normalidad de wescol Y esto
is not 2013 this is yesterday this is the day before
no es 2013 esto es ayer esto antes de
yesterday that I turn out trans dude there dic
ayer queo me salga trans huevón ahí dic
Oh no what the [ __ ] is wrong with that son of a [ __ ]
Ay no qué [__] le pasa ese hijo de [__]
why doesn't he want his son to fall for him at
porque no quiere que su hijo le calga at
This was when the debate with Dallas it
Esto fue cuando el debate con Dallas no
was more or less that time or so it was
fue más o menos esa época o sea est hace
a year or two ago I don't know how much I don't want it
un año o dos no sé cuánto no quiero
dude now they're going to criticize me because I don't
huevón ahora me van a criticar porque no
want my son to bring me up trans now
quiero que mi hijo me traiga trans ahora
if my son turns out trans it's very
si mi hijo me sale trans ya muy
different what would my reaction be
diferente cuál sería mi reacción
obviously my reaction is going to be to support him
obviamente mi reacción va a ser apoyarlo
support him against one and shove a stick up his
apoyarlo contra una y metle un palo por
ass so he sees that it's not
el culo para que vea que eso no es
good that my friend turns out trans
bueno que amigo me salga trans
dude and well to finish this
huevón y bueno para terminar con este
mess let's see Nis giving his opinion a
trasto vamos a ver a nis opinando un
little about the fights it's the
poco sobre los combates es el combate
most unbalanced fight I've seen
más desbalanceado que he visto
eh since mine and Alana's I mean
eh desde el mío y el de alana o sea
honestly I mean it's [ __ ] crazy I
sinceramente o sea es una [__] locura o
mean eh Let's see
sea eh A ver
no  no no no a guy who just
no no no no va a luchar un tío que se
ran a [ __ ] marathon who
acaba de correr una [__] maratón que
plays sports every [ __ ] day of his
hace deporte Todos los [__] días de su
life is going to fight against a person who, well, you
vida contra una persona que bueno se
can say it No dude, he said that, he didn't
puede decir No chavi eso lo dijo él no
say it, yes I mean he just quit smoking
lo dijo él si O sea que se acaba de
joints,
dejar los porros
the bad life, whoremonger or whatever, terrible,
de la mala vida [__] o sea terrible
all the bad life, I mean he just
todo todo la mala vida o sea se acaba de
quit the bad life to get into a
dejar la mala vida para subirse a un
[ __ ] ring against a person who
[__] ring contra una persona que se
just ran a marathon, I
acaba de correr una maratón plan me
think it's [ __ ] crazy to me, man, I think he
parece una putísima locura tío creo que
's completely
está completamente
unbalanced, I'm sure he's going to
desbalanceado yo tengo Claro que le va a
kick his ass, he's
partir la cara
going to blow it up I think it's really
eh se lo va a reventar se me hace muy
ugly that everyone is
feo que ande todo el mundo
criticizing social media because he gained
criticando redes porque haya subido de
weight, yeah, he does have a chubby face
peso que sí que que tiene la cara más
but I don't know, man, they're criticizing
gordita pero no sé tío están criticando
Lana for her physique, seriously, they're
a lana por el físico en serio están
doing an edit with Mister Potato, my God,
haciendo edit con Mister potato por Dios
how could she be pregnant? The thing
cómo va a estar embarazada Lo que pasa
is, if you have
es que si tú tienes unos músculos
huge muscles and you gain a little bit of weight, Well,
enormes y coges un poquito de peso Pues
you look a little rounder, man. But that
te ves un poco más redondo tío Pero eso
doesn't mean that the girl is not
no significa que la chica ni esté
pregnant or fat or anything,
embarazada ni sea una gorda ni nada por
because  the style I mean the girl She's still
por el estilo O sea la chica Sigue
amazing she has a great ass I
estando estupenda tiene un culazo cabrón
mean what the [ __ ] am I looking at the picture
O sea qué coj e estoy mir la foto la
they're criticizing Lana for her physique
están criticando a lana por el físico en
seriously poor Tyrion quit smoking joints Look
serio pobre tyrion dejo los porros Mira
well Tyrion could go up and fight at the
pues tyrion podría subirse a pelear a la
party eh man let's see
velada eh hombre a ver
forgive me but objectively she's a
perdonadme pero objetivamente es una
girl who is very good No I couldn't
chica que está muy bien No no podría
say that the Spanish treat
decir que los españoles tratan mal a los
Latinos or Colombians badly because I haven't
latinos o a los colombianos porque yo no
been there but it's true that
he ido allá pero si es cierto que
we Colombians welcome
nosotros los colombianos recibimos bien
foreigners Especially those of us who are
a los extranjeros Especialmente los que
from
somos de
but it's not because of being a foreigner or Spanish or from
pero no es por ser extranjero ni español
anywhere it's not because of that it's because of the
parte sea no es por eso es por el
history okay let's see man this is a
historial vale a ver tío esto es una
girl who is spectacular No
chica que está espectacular No
objectively yes she is a little bit more
objetivamente sí está un poquito más
[Music]
[Música]
anchotena
anchotena
Lana has gone up I mean what can you
lana ha subido o sea cómo podéis
call this girl fat She's
llamarle a esta chica gorda Está
incredible man I
increíble tío
mean Look at that ass like She's
o sea Mirad ese culazo en plan Está
incredible guys I mean Stop
increíble cabrones O sea Dejad de
calling Lana fat because yes she's not
llamarle a lana gorda que sí que no está
as thin as last time but but what do
tan delgada como la última vez pero pero
I know man like the body of  a
yo que sé tío en plan el cuerpo de una
person is not always the same you know it's
persona no siempre es igual sab es
impossible to always be the same it's
imposible estar siempre igual es
impossible you know I mean there are
imposible sabes o sea hay unas
times when they are a little thinner eh
temporadas que están más delgaditos eh
live for your body look I am
vivir para tu cuerpo yo mira yo soy
incapable with the life that I have of living
incapaz con la vida que tengo de llevar
what I wanted when I got with
lo que yo quería cuando yo me puse con
the trainer and with the diet I'm not
el entrenador y con la dieta esto no lo
going to fail this I'm going to live for this
voy a fallar yo voy a vivir para esto
a dick today I had to take the girl
una [__] hoy tenía que llevar a la niña
to the doctor for some things for the girl
al médico para unas cosas de la niña
okay things of girl things
vale cosas de cosas de de chicas
eh Tomorrow I have something with him No
eh Mañana tengo una cosa con el No
lie tomorrow I do have something with the
mentira mañana sí tengo una cosa con el
boy with the extracurricular activities of the thing that
niño de la extraescolar de la cosa que
of the things that he does I don't know how much
de las cosas que él hace no sé cuánto
boom at the gym time I haven't
pum a la hora del gimnasio llevo sin
trained since Friday I haven't
entrenar desde el viernes llevo sin
trained since Friday when I don't
entrenar desde el viernes cuando no me
one thing happens to me another happens I don't know what
pasa una cosa pasa la otra no sé qué no
you can't the the people with
puedes la la las personas con las vidas
normal lives again he's a little fatter
normales otra vez que está más gordito
but the girl She's still incredible I mean she
pero la chica Sigue estando increíble o
's impressive I mean what the [ __ ]
sea está impresionante O sea qué [__]
chat No they're not excuses for anything Eric I
chat No no son excusas para nada Eric yo
have the training at 5 in the afternoon and it
tengo el entrenado a las 5 de la tarde y
's impossible to do it at another time I mean
y es imposible hacerlo a otra hora o sea
no I don't have another time that I can
no no tengo otra hora en la que lo pueda
do it  I'm here at night maybe it has
hacer yo estoy aquí por la noche a lo
cost me now that 3 or 4
mejor me ha cuesto ahora que las 3 las 4
yes I'm recording a video for the
si Estoy grabando un vídeo para el
main one many times 4 4 something you
principal muchas veces las 4 4 y pico
know I'm not going to get up at 10
sabes yo no me voy a levantar a las 10
in the morning you know what I mean In the
de la mañana me entiendes Yo por la
morning what I do is take the dog out
mañana lo que hago es sacar al perro
make the beds eh and then in no time
hacer las camas eh y ya luego en nada
running I have the time to pick up
corriendo tengo la hora de recoger a
these people from classes to Lorena the
esta gente de de la clases a Lorena los
kids from school okay And when I go
niños del colegio vale Y yo cuando voy
is after lunch After lunch I
es después de comer Yo después de comer
prepare a few things here not
preparo aquí un poquito de cositas no
the live shows whatever you do and
los directos lo que te hagas hac y
then and then then I go to the gym and
luego y luego luego me voy a gimnasio y
then When I come back from the gym well or I spend
luego Cuando vengo de gimnasio pues o
some time with him with the boyfriend or
bien Estoy un rato con el con el chico o
whatever I don't know but I have to go I
lo que sea yo que sé pero tengo que ir
organize my day to have time for
Voy organizando mi día para tener tiempo
everything but in the end my
de todo pero al final mi tiempo de
work time is the hours that I am at
trabajo son las horas que estoy por la
night How many hours have I been here today How many
noche Cuántas horas llevo hoy Cuántas
hours How many hours have I been here today I mean today I
horas Cuántas horas llevo hoy o sea hoy
did the live show the first one for the
he hecho el directo el primero del
main one that was recorded that one I
principal ese estaba grabado ese me
got up in the morning at 101 around there
levanté por la mañana a las 101 por ahí
to record it because with that  Man, we have to meet up
para grabarlo porque con ese hombre hay
with Javier in the morning. Urra.
que quedar por la mañana con Javier urra
Okay, so I'm sleeping about 5
Vale entonces estoy durmiendo hoy unas 5
hours today, which I slept last night, okay, 4, 5 hours I
horas que dormí anoche vale 4 5 horas
recorded. I've been tied up all day
grabé Ya he estado todo el día ligado
with things, pin Pam Pam, you know, and then the
con las cosas pin Pam Pam sabes y luego
real live shows, the real live shows
ya de directos reales de directos reales
are the one I did with Trium, for almost an
son el que he hecho con trium casi una
hour and a half, the one we did on
hora y media el que hemos hecho en
Telesalseo, I don't know how long it was, and the one
telesalseo no sé cuánto tiempo hací y el
we did,
que hemos hecho
uh. And the one we're doing now, I
eh Y el que estamos haciendo ahora todo
prepared all of this, uh, I've been spending
esto lo he preparado yo eh yo he estado
an hour or two preparing the live shows,
una hora o dos preparando los directos
the content for the live shows because
los contenidos de los directos porque
Luare isn't there. Okay, if I had to, if I had to
luare no está Vale Si tuviera Si tuviera
record a video for the
que grabar ahora un vídeo para el
main show now. Now when I finish the salsería, that
principal Ahora cuando acabo la salsería
's when I record the video for the
es cuando yo grabo el vídeo del
main show that you guys see in the morning, I
principal que lo veis por la mañana o
mean, I don't have any other
sea no tengo otra
time. Rober, man, my goodness, in the end, the
hora Rober tío madre mía al final el
thing about living for, for a workout, for
tema de vivir para para un entreno para
a diet, of course, someone like Gref, his
una dieta claro alguien como gref es su
girlfriend, doesn't have children, lives there quietly,
novia no tiene hijos vive allí tranquilo
Chile, in Andorra, you know. No, no, it's not the
chile en andorra sabes No no es lo
same, nobody. But why? Because
mismo nadie Pero por qué Porque es que
if I told someone, they'd leak it,
si se lo cuento a alguien lo filtraban
Auron knew it, no, no.  auron didn't know that's why
auron lo sabía no no auron no lo sabía
when you see the clip yes, there's
por eso cuando veis el clip sí a mí hay
a moment where some of the
un momento que me sobra alguno de los
content is left out but I don't know which one it will be, I
contenidos pero no sé cuál será yo me
imagine it will be, I have no idea, it
imagino que será no tengo ni idea
depends Carmen.
dependerá Carmen Muchas
Thank you very much for what auron says, eh. But
gracias este que dice auron eh Pero
well, it won't be in the very near future, right now it's
bueno no será en un futuro muy próximo
also going well
que ahora mismo también va bien en todos
everywhere, I mean, everything is going well, the
lados o sea todo va bien va la
gentlemen are going right now It's nothing, I mean,
señoreros ahora mismo No es nada o sea
the day that I can't, well, I can't, well, that's it, you
el día que no pueda que pues no puedo
know, eh. There are very
pues ya está sabes eh Hay combates Muy
nice fights and people who don't expect it and they say and
guapos y gente que no se espera y dice y
by hostia eh
by [__] eh
but but damn, something like that surprised me
pero pero ostia me ha sorprendido algo
no no s he said I said something like it
así no no s dijo I dijo algo como me
surprises me what's up and Auro cuts him
sorprende que tal y Auro le corta Auro
off. Auro cuts him off, don't continue because if you
le corta del rollo no sigas Porque si
continue, they'll find out that it's someone I
sigues van a saber que es alguien que
know. So I'm
conozco
telling you. There he cuts him off, that's why,
entonces ya os digo Ahí le corta por eso
not because of another fight, because they're going to cut him off.
no por otro combate por le van a cortar
I mean, of course, people thought because it
me refiero claro la gente pensaba porque
was because of someone else, but no, it wasn't because of mine
era por otro pero no no era por el mío
because of course, but I'm telling you that
porque claro por pero os digo que no lo
nobody knew, nobody from the
sabía nadie nadie de
internet, nobody. But not for nothing. It's more,
internet nadie Pero no por nada Es más
you know how people found out, already on the
sabéis cómo se enteró la gente ya de
internet, let's say, people  from the internet people
internet digamos gente de internet gente
of the Kings people of Well that spursito
de la Kings gente de Pues eso spursito
Juan Juan Mario
Juan Juan Mario
wanar I will always remember perchita as
wanar siempre recordaré a perchita como
the guy who gave a
el tío que le regaló una cerda
Vietnamese pig to his girlfriend you know that
vietnamita a la novia ustedes sabéis
I don't know if they still have the pig
eso yo no sé si siguen teniendo el cerdo
everything that happened yesterday was totally real eh
todo lo que pasó ayer fue full real eh
I had talked a little bit with him before it's just that we do
yo había hablado un poquito antes con él
n't know each other It's no wonder we do
es que tampoco no nos conocemos De nada
n't know each other It's no wonder a little when he
no nos conocemos De nada un poco cuando
wrote to me it was around December or
a mí me escribió iba en diciembre más o
so he said Hey Pereira I want you to I
menos me dijo Oye Pereira quiero que te
want you to Hit each other at the evening I want you to
quiero que te Pegues en la velada quiero
have a fight for me It was
que tengas un combate para mí Fue
incredible So tell me an opponent at
increíble Entonces dime un rival yo de
first I asked him Juan Guarnizo I said
primeras le pedí Juan guarnizo le dije
give me Juan Guarnizo the one I want to
ponme a Juan guarnizo al que quiero
beat is the [ __ ] Juan Guarnizo and
cargarme es al putísimo Juan guarnizo y
Juan rejected him then rival God came out
y lo rechazó Juan luego salió rival Dios
and at the same time he came out Juan rejected him eh I
y a la par salió lo rechazó Juan eh o
mean Juan the whole time rejecting
sea Juan todo el tiempo rechazando
fights
combates
the creature has been rejecting the whole
ha estado la criatura rechazando todo el
time possibly next to a Frenchman and poses
tiempo posil lado un francés y poses
silado an American What's up French
silado un estadunidense Qué pasa francés
and
y
American I wanted to take the Flow
estadunidense yo quería llevar el Flow
that I took yesterday and what and what I want to
que llevé ayer y que y que quiero que
happen  Hey I want the fight to have substance I
pase Eh quiero que la pelea tenga chicha
want the fight to have desire It's that
quiero que la pelea tenga ganas Es que
I feel that there has to be blood there has to be
yo siento que tiene que haber sangre
punches there has to be anger and this one is going to
tiene que haber hostias tiene que haber
kill the other one eh he's going to
pique n lo va a matar este al otro eh lo
kill him the other one done
va a matar hecha el otro
Oh lazy no why don't you fight because I already
Ay peresa no por qu no peleas porque ya
fought twice I'm not a
peleé dos veces
boxer anymore No I'm a
ya ya no soy boxeadora No yo soy
streamer I'm a creator
streamer soy creora
content it was good It turned out well why
contenido estuvo bien Quedó bien para
move it why touch it gy What for
qué moverle para qué tocarlo gy Para qué
what and that's what he has to do
para qué y eso es lo que tiene que hacer
I showed what I wanted to
enseñé lo que quería
show that's it what Perea
enseñar ya está qué Perea
Okay family let's
Bueno familia a
see they're also talking Jorge Javi
ver también están hablando jorgo Javi
all the ones from Galicia are like
todos los de Galicia son así de
ghosts no no but Pereira is going to
fantasmas no no pero el Pereira le va a
blow up the other one eh let's see you can
reventar al otro eh sea se le ve se le
see the bug eh you can see it you can
ve el [__] eh se le ve se le ve se le
see that he's
ve que está
crazy you can see that he's strung out and that he's
corado se le ve que está colgado y que
going to blow up the
va a reventar al
other one Let's see Gaspi Gaspi I've never seen him in my
otro A ver gaspi gaspi no lo he visto en
life eh Javi don't speak ill of Gapi
la vida eh Javi no hables mal de Gapi
please man let's see he doesn't make it
por favor hombre a ver no me lo pone
easy for me touch I mean no I haven't investigated
fácil toca O sea no no he investigado
yet  I think we
todavía Creo que muy probablemente
can probably funeral the whole evening
podamos funar a toda la velada entera
okay but but watch this video I'm
vale pero pero mirar este vídeo soy
lazy And unfortunately my grandmother is about to
gaspi Y lamentablemente mi abuela se
die but since I'm a good
está por morir pero como soy un buen
grandson I'm going to buy her a good coffin
Nieto le voy a comprar un buen cajón
as it
como
should be on the website Corona
corresponde en la página Corona
funebre.com Oh grandma the truth is I don't have the
funebre.com Ay abuela la verdad no tengo
gas to do this but I'm going to have to
gas de hacer esto pero voy a tener que
do it anyway But what are you doing Ah I'm
hacer Igual Pero qué hacés Ah te estoy
measuring you for the coffin because I didn't measure your
midiendo para el cajón por no te medí la
dick because you don't like the coffin
pija qué lo que es el cajo no te gusta
Why don't you die you suck V let's see what
Por qué no te morís vos chup V a ver lo
the smell of the dead grandma is like look how
que es el olor al muerto abuela mira lo
pretty it's going to look inside the
linda que vaya a quedar adentro del
coffin Oh Lu eaten by the guaitos How I'm
cajón Oh Lu comida por los guanitos Cómo
going to laugh my ass off when you
me voy a [__] de risa cuando vos te
die
mueras
my law will win first V keep
primero va a ganar mi ley V seguí
voting for more for grandma Look I brought you
votando a mása pel abuela Mira Te traje
a stripper turn off the light
un striper apágame la luz
Yeah and grandma you
Sí y abuela te
liked it mother what a son of a [ __ ]
gustó madre que te hijo de con de tu
but good You don't like anything that I
madre pero buena Nada te gustaa que te
'm giving you a coffin worth 400,000 pesos
estoy regalando un cajón de 400000 pesos
Who told you that I want a coffin I
Quién te dijo que yo quiero un cajón yo
want to be cremated Yeah come on I'll cremate you And
quiero que me cremen Sí dale te cremo Y
where do I throw  the cilla in a place in
dónde tiro la cilla en un lugar de
artina there are
artina
only 10 units left and
solo quedan 10 unidades y ya está hecha
the publication has already been made in mercado libre Look
la publicación en mercado libre Mira
hurry up there are only 10 eh for
Apúrense que solo hay 10 eh para
decoration for Bono and to make some
decoración para Bono y para hacer unas
delicious
ricas
milanesas but let's see did the grandmother really die
milanesas pero a ver murió la abuela de
or did she not appear anymore
verdad o no apareció más
simply a very dark humor no but
simplemente un humor muy negro no pero
listen to me let's see but let's see but did the
escúchame a ver pero a ver pero murió la
grandmother really die or was she fired and
abuela de verdad o la despidió y la
removed from
quitó de la vida
public life she went to
pública se fue a la
[ __ ] let's see for the moment no I have not
[__] a ver de momento no no he
found something as funable no like
encontrado algo como tan funable no como
for that no
para eso no